♪ In the not-too-distant future
♪ Somewhere in time and space
♪ Mike Nelson and his robot pals
♪ Are caught in a nasty place
♪ They try to survive
the wrath of Pearl
♪ Just an evil gal who
wants to rule the world
♪ From her castle below
she sets her sights above
♪ Just to torture
all the captives on
the Satellite of Love
- [Mike] Get me down!
♪ I'll send them cheesy movies
♪ The worst I can find
♪ La-la-la
♪ They'll have to sit
and watch them all
♪ And the monitor is mine
♪ La-la-la
♪ Now keep in mind
Mike can't control
♪ Where the movies begin or end
♪ La-la-la
♪ He'll try to keep his sanity
♪ With the help of
his robot friends
♪ Robot roll call
♪ Cambot
- You're on.
♪ Gypsy
- Oh my stars!
♪ Tom Servo
- Check me out.
♪ Croooow
- I'm different.
♪ If you're wondering
how he eats and breathes
♪ And other science facts
♪ La-la-la
♪ Just repeat to
yourself, it's just a show
♪ I should really just relax
♪ For Mystery
Science Theater 3000
(doors slamming)
- Son of a--
Mike!
Crow, a little help?
I can't==
- What's the matter, Servo?
- I was cleaning out my room,
and something got stuck
in my hover skirt,
and now I'm not
getting any lift.
- Oh, let's get out of it.
- Whoa!
There.
- Well, look at this.
It's an SOL Employee Handbook.
- Huh, what do you know?
- I've never seen this before.
"Welcome to the Forrester
Family of Hostages.
"Making your life miserable
for over nine years."
- Wow.
- Nice.
- It covers everything.
Discrimination policy.
"I reserve the right
to discriminate
"against anyone I
want, especially Mike."
- Figures.
- Benefits package.
"All employees are entitled
to smooch my backside."
- What does it say
about grievances?
- Hmm, let me see here.
Oh, grievance procedures.
"Make your hand
into a hard fist,
"drawing as far away from
your face as possible,
"and keep your hand in place.
"Quickly and forcefully
run toward your hand."
- Well, we'll be right back.
- Hey!
- Yeah.
- Heh.
(Mystery Science
Theater 3000 theme)
- Does it say anything
about our dental coverage?
- "Shut up, you have
no right to ask!"
- Sorry, Mike, I didn't think
you'd take it so personally!
- No, no, that's what
it says in the...
(loud creaking)
- Whoa, whoa, whoa!
- Hey, hey!
- What the heck?
- What the hell?
What's going on here?
- We better find
out what's going on!
Hey, Pearl's up!
- Oh, hi, Nike Melson.
How do you like my new joystick?
Got it at Radio Shack.
Say, I was wondering,
what does a high-speed
tumble do to your stomach?
(everyone groaning)
I am just messing
with everybody today!
(nefarious giggling)
What'd I do?
- Hang on now!
- Feel sick.
- Oh, boy!
- Hey, you guys, the
retrofire has been activated,
and the ship's initiating
a reentry protocol!
- What?
- Prepare for
gravitational reinsertion!
- Mike!
This means we're
headed to Earth!
- Earth, that's my home!
- Yes, yes!
- Isn't it?
- Yes.
- Earth!
- To Earth!
(joyous laughter)
(Crow vomiting)
Crow, you're
wrecking the moment!
- [Crow] I'm sorry!
(frustrated groan)
- Apparently, you initiated
reentry protocol
for the satellite.
- Well, make it not
protocol to reentry!
Make it better!
- Well, you broke
off the stick of joy.
It's irreversible and wet bread.
- You're omnipotent!
Do something!
- Pearl, the Mountain Dew
you so playfully poured
into my brain pan took
my gravitational control
as well as my speech centers.
Table-dog-purple-liquefy.
- No, damn it, no!
They will not escape me!
I'll see them dead first!
- Hey, Lawgiver, why
don't you just take
and use the Satellite's
self-destruct mechanism?
- We have one?
- Yeah, right there.
- Bobo, I'm a genius!
Take this, losers!
- Chili squint!
(Bobo growling)
(rapid beeping)
- This is it, I love you, Crow,
I love you, Servo,
I love you, Gypsy.
- I love you, Mike, I love
you, Servo, I love you, Crow.
- I love you, Gypsy, I love
you, Mike, I love you, Servo.
- I love you, Gypsy,
I love you, Mike.
(extended beep)
(tiny explosion)
- Oh.
- Um, Servo, do you wanna--
- I was gonna say it!
I just couldn't
think of your name!
- Yeah, right.
- Well, the Satellite of
Love is headed back to Earth.
Paper, northbound, feet.
- It's as good as
done, Lawgiver.
- Nooooo!
No!
(furious sobbing)
- Oh!
- This can't be good for us!
- No.
(furious sobbing)
(loud smack)
- See?
- [Pearl] Oh, god!
- Raging clip art.
- Reentry commencing!
Entering low orbit.
We'll be landing in one
hour and 55 minutes.
- Hooray!
- Yay!
- We did it!
We did it!
- Well, I mean, we didn't
really do it, but...
- Well, it was done by someone!
- Yes, someone did it!
- It was done!
- Yay!
- Woooooo!
- Hurrah!
- Hoo, hoo, hoo, hoo!
- There, there.
Ooh.
- Oh.
So you're coming
back to Earth, huh?
So I failed, huh?
(primal scream)
(panicked scream)
That's fine!
It's okay!
Good for you!
But there's still one
button that works,
so you're still getting
your final movie.
I give you...
Diabolik!
If it gives you half the hell
I have had to endure
keeping you captive,
it will have all been worth it.
(quiet sobbing)
(alarm buzzing)
- Oh, movie sign, let's go!
- Boy, we're not gonna be
hearing that back on Earth.
- Yeah, let's enjoy it.
- Yeah.
- Will you get in there, please?
- Boy, we're not gonna
be hearing that either.
- Wow.
- Let's enjoy it.
- Come on!
(puzzled groan)
(doors opening)
(sonar beeping)
- [Mike] Oh, my.
Two Fat Ladies have
their own gang now.
(sirens wailing)
- [Servo] Uh, the
hyena is stuck on.
- [Crow] Oh no, is this
a Pink Floyd video?
- [Mike] Dr. Pepper formula
requires very high security.
- [Servo] At least it's a
nice orderly bank robbery.
- Alright, how are we doing?
- Well, last bag.
- [Crow] Uniforms designed
by William Rehnquist.
- All plain paper.
Wonder how those guys
would feel if they knew
they were guarding
all this wastepaper
instead of $10
million, huh, sir?
- [Mike] They'd feel hurt, sir.
- Well, that's it.
- [Servo] Sergeant
Sideburns reporting.
(shrill whistling)
- [Crow] Just watching you film.
Don't worry about me.
- [Servo] If Hitler had won
and hired Stu Sutcliffe
as a fashion designer.
- [Mike] Malcolm Forbes
and friends go camping.
- [Crow] Good luck with
the movie, you guys.
- [Mike] Mike Brady
World Headquarters.
- We're ready.
- [Servo] We need your
desk to make sandwiches.
(motorcycle engines roaring)
- [Crow] Spring Break!
- [Servo] Woo-hoo!
- This is the largest single
shipment of dollars ever made
at six o'clock in the morning.
- [Mike] There was a
larger one at 7 a.m. once.
- Would you please
sign here, inspector?
- Right.
- I've never seen
such precautions just
to reach the port.
- The whole underworld worries
me less than a single man.
- [Servo] Michael Jeter.
- Diabolik?
(dramatic music)
- Excuse me.
They're waiting
for you, inspector.
- Good luck.
- Ah, hah.
- [Mike] Well, that was
an inappropriate response.
- [Crow] Yeah.
(dramatic music)
A Scrooge McDuck fortune.
- [Servo] Boy, Lech
Walesa is rich!
- Well, that makes
exactly $10 million.
Alright, you can take that away.
Here.
- [Mike] Oh, I'm gonna
feed this bag to the dog.
(upbeat music)
- [Crow] Mmm, I
really do have a cud!
(chewing noises)
(Servo humming)
- [Mike] Oh, there it goes, the
liquid center just exploded.
Oh.
- [Servo] The Young
Mr. Boston Story.
- [Mike] Sir, are you
trying to seduce me?
(Servo humming music)
- [Crow] Ah, there's
some crap all over me!
What the hell is this stuff?
- Well.
- [Servo] When I said
dress up real tough,
this is what you come up with?
- [Ginko] This is wonderful.
Just splendid.
- [Mike] Duh, anyone
want to marry me?
- And dignified, too.
Are they meant to be diplomats?
- They're the best men we have.
- Uh-huh.
- We did this.
- You're a diplomat?
Look sophisticated.
- [Crow] Sophisticated, not gay!
- You're a man of the world.
Polished, witty, bored.
What's that?
- [Mike] You have a chili stain!
- Here, put it in your hat.
And these.
(Servo belching)
Alright, let's go.
(uptempo surf music)
♪ Driving off to the store
♪ Gonna pick up some bread
♪ Maybe stop by the post office
♪ Meet Dolores for lunch
♪ Hope they're serving
that ham, oh yeah
- [Servo] Each seagull
has its own parking space.
- [Mike] Michael, we're lost.
- [Crow] This music
would work better
with women in bikinis
shaking all over the place.
I think that's true
of any music, really.
- [Mike] They're going over to
John Steed's house for a kegger.
(dramatic music)
- [Servo] Wild thing!
- [Mike] Doo doo
doo-doo doo, doo-doo.
Man, that is one Europey road.
- [Man] This is Air
Surveillance Ship Number One.
Now over port zone.
Nothing suspicious,
repeat, nothing suspicious.
Embarkation to
proceed as scheduled.
Over.
- [Ginko] Ginko here.
Have received.
(horn whooping)
- [Crow] Would somebody shut
those howler monkeys up?
(horn blowing)
- [Servo]
Beeeeeeeeeeeeeeeee-ohhhhhhhhh!
(horn whooping)
- [Crow] Whooping.
Cranes.
What?
- [Mike] Dah, giant
robotic seahorses!
- [Servo] Some movies
just won't stop
and ask for directions.
(gas hissing)
- [Mike] Clown gas.
(ethereal music)
- [Crow] Joni Mitchell
must be nearby.
(tires screeching)
- What the?
- [Man] Inspector?
What's happening?
Inspector!
- [Mike] It's the Dick
Butkus newspaper grill!
- [Man] Stay with
the Rolls Royce!
- [Servo] Boy, Ted, when you
let one, you don't kid around!
- [Crow] Hey, you're
having sex with me!
Now cut that out!
- [Mike] Sorry!
- [Ginko] Oh, no.
Where's the Rolls?
- [Man] It disappeared!
- [Ginko] What's
that, you moron?
- [Man] Inspector, we
tried (coughing)...
And it was gone just like that!
- [Man] There it is!
- [Mike] The Rolls
is going to heaven.
Another great car.
- [Servo] They're downwind
of the Rainbow Gathering.
- [Crow] And still,
Union Carbide claims
they're meeting all guidelines.
- [Men] Diabolik!
(ethereal music)
- [Mike] Starring
this Muslim woman.
- [Servo] When he takes
that mask off later,
his weird tan will
give him away.
(diabolic laughter)
- [Crow] Okay, yeah,
it's not that funny.
(rapid gunshots)
- [Mike] Here's
all your laundry.
(rapid gunshots)
♪ Deep, deep, down
- [Servo] Uh-oh,
it's getting groovy.
- [Crow] Oh god, is
someone gonna tell us
that something is
shagadelic, man?
- [Servo] Oh, no, no.
♪ Deep, deep, down
- [Mike] A-wheel of fortuna.
- [Servo] Uh-oh.
Mike, I need my Dramamine.
- [Crow] Mario Donen.
Renzo Palmer.
- [Mike] Never start a movie
in the middle of the spin cycle.
- [Crow] Starring a bunch
of vowels and Terry Thomas.
- [Mike] Well, thank goodness
they had three
people on soggetto.
- [Crow] The true
story of Spin Art.
- [Mike] Man, I feel
sicker than when I went
on the tilt-a-whirl
10 times in a row.
- [Servo] Movie just started,
it's already circling the drain.
- [Crow] I must agree, by the
way, dee-dee-dah, absolutely.
- [Servo] Slam enough espresso,
and you'll see the
world like this.
♪ Deep down, he
might love deep down
♪ Very deep, deep down
- [Crow] This must be from
the point of view of
a Scrubbing Bubble.
♪ No, womp-ba-doo
(Servo scatting)
- [Mike] The wall,
I are, deep down.
♪ Very deep, deep down
♪ You, only you, deep down
- [Servo] A French-Italian
co-production, so I'm guessing
there's gonna be a lot
of cheese involved here.
♪ Keep my heart deep down
- [Mike] Keep my potty down?
Women and their
toilet seat issues.
- [Servo] Under his firm and
visionary diretto, I feel safe.
- [Crow] Gentlemen,
let's open our movie
with a 10-minute shot
of a spinning radish.
- [Mike] Reverse Raccoon Man!
♪ All I want is you
- [Servo] I can't breathe.
(muffled breathing)
(Mystery Science
Theater 3000 theme)
- [Crow] I never should have let
that balloon melt on my face.
- [Mike] Diabolik
is late for daycare.
- [Servo] Honey, you
forgot your lunch!
(muffled speech)
(rapid gunfire)
- [Mike] Wisconsin
kill speeders.
(tires screeching)
- [Servo] Run that
metered ramp, will ya?
- [Crow] Is this
the one circumstance
where driving drunk
is actually safer?
- [Mike] They have a bowling
ball glued to their runner.
(tires screeching)
- [Crow] Whoa,
where are we going?!
Hey, look out!
- [Mike] Hey, we're
going in (vomits).
- Hey, helicopter one
through to Coast Patrol.
Helicopter one through
to Coast Patrol.
Attention, attention.
Jaguar spotted.
Turned off main highway headed
towards senior district.
- Roger, affirmative.
- [Crow] Do something
affirmative, Roger.
(helicopter whirring)
- [Mike]
Da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da,
this guy!
- [Servo] Hey look,
that's pretty.
- [Mike] Oh, a lot of drift
on this steering wheel.
(rapid gunfire)
(bullets ricocheting)
- [Crow] Ah, this is a metaphor
for arterial plaque reduction.
(tires screeching)
- [Mike] Good thing Britt
Ekland is waiting for him.
(tires screeching)
- [Servo] Ah-ha, my
licorice suit held up well.
- Eva.
- [Crow] Thanks for
helping me, Mom.
(helicopter whirring)
- [Servo] Hey, dammit.
- [Crow] Make the
tunnel entrance
look like a slice of bread.
(rapid gunfire)
(tires screeching)
- [Mike] George
Jones tours Italy.
- [Servo] Uh,
you're flooding it.
(ethereal music)
- [Crow] Tar fashions never
really took off, did they?
- [Mike] Owwww,
that was my skin!
♪ Deep, deep, down
- [Crow] Deep, deep tongue.
- [Servo] I'm driving
with my whipper.
- [Crow] Hmm, I don't know, a
white car before Memorial Day?
- [Servo] Risky, huh?
(high-pitched squeaking)
Stop playing with that balloon.
- [Mike] Ah, a giant earth
clam is attacking them!
- [Servo] This will fool
them unless they look at it.
(midtempo mysterious music)
- [Crow] You know, it's
hard to get contractors
who will do this kind of work,
signing the complete
secrecy agreement
on pain of death and all.
(engine revving)
- [Servo] You may get nauseous
and light-headed froe
the exhaust fumes,
but still, pretty cool, huh?
- [Crow] Great
hideout, but it's hard
to get your Sunday
paper delivered.
- [Mike] They had Willy Wonka's
contractor do this part.
- [Crow] Yeah, you go
through Mop and Glo
by the case keeping
this place shiny.
- [Servo] Did you really
need this much stuff
to get some tail in the '60s?
I thought a hi-fi
would do the job.
♪ Deep, deep down
- [Mike] I have an
awning over my cyke.
Like it?
♪ Deep, deep down
- [Servo] A tanning
lamp works better
if you get out of the car.
♪ Deep, deep down
- [Mike] We're out of gas.
- [Crow] Mmm-hmm, mmm-hmm, good.
Okay, okay, okay.
Alright, and you
have those, too.
That's fine.
Pretty good.
- [Servo] Let's have
a tantric quickie.
- [Mike] Oh, you smell
like a tire store.
- [Servo] This is
just a Good Samaritan
he met in the tunnel.
- [Crow] She's a
Great Samaritan!
- [Servo] You don't mind if
I swallow your face, do you?
- [Mike] Oh, oh.
Sorry, some unexpected rubbing
in the outfit, so I, well...
(engine droning)
- [Crow] Pretty fancy-schmancy
Jiffy Lube they go to.
- [Servo] This is
just my mud room.
- [Mike] Wow.
Occasionally, a spelunker
just wanders in.
"Hey, what the hell?"
- [Crow] Let me just go and
have really quick lousy sex.
(sensual mysterious music)
(Servo humming)
(sniffing air)
- [Mike] Oh, you have cats, huh?
- [Servo] You gonna help me
with the groceries, or...
- [Mike] He loves her so much,
he bought her a walk-in diamond.
- [Crow] Hmmm, I
love your Habitrail.
- [Servo] You need
some baseboard heaters
in this tunnel.
It's freezing in here!
- [Mike] Please get Ravi
Shankar out of the living room!
- [Crow] Oh, I
need to get out of
these bulky,
restricting clothes.
I am so bunched
up in this thing.
- [Mike] Wow,
dangerously steep stairs.
- [Servo] You're
watching the stairs?
Poor Mike.
- Oh, Mike.
Gee whiz.
- What?
- [Crow] I oughta take
down that Simon game
I superglued on the ceiling.
- [Servo] Considering the
guy who owned it before
had a North Woods theme going,
I think he's done pretty well.
(electronic beep)
(electronic droning)
- [Mike] High-tech
for a bathroom fan.
(electronic droning)
- [Crow] Really makes the hall
to our theater look efficient.
- [Servo] Might as well throw
these Hardee's wrappers
away now I'm here.
- [Crow] Oh, I can't
wait to get into
my loose-fitting latex sweats.
(Servo humming)
- [Servo] Turns out
he's just house-sitting.
- [Crow] Yeah, he
actually lives in
an efficiency over at the
campus with some guys.
- [Mike] Well, my cherry
tomato detector's operational.
Good.
(air hissing)
- [Servo] Oh, damn,
blew the place up again.
Gotta learn the combination.
- [Crow] I went out
to get something.
What was it...
Oh, bread!
Dammit.
- [Mike] He's pretending
to be The Pretender.
- [Crow] I really should
get a checking account.
- [Mike] Well, I'm just
delaying the moment
she finds out I have an
undescended testicle.
(engine turning)
(upbeat sensual music)
- [Servo] Ugh, they're
really gonna have
to get their money laundered.
- [Crow] Steve
Forbes and his wife.
- [Mike] With my budget,
I'd be rolling around
in a handful of change.
- [Servo] Oh, the
paper cuts are brutal.
- [Mike] (gagging) I have
100 caught in my throat.
- [Crow] A young Alan Greenspan.
- [Servo] They got
pretty badly injured
when they tried
this with gold bars.
- [Mike] When they make
love in English pound notes,
the sex is 50% better.
- [Servo] Oh, you're
the friendliest
teller I've ever met.
Last time, I just got a toaster.
- [Crow] Y'know, if he'd
stolen just a little less,
I could see her ass right now.
Good grief.
- [Servo] Member,
FDIC, heh-heh-heh-heh.
(doors slamming)
(sonar beeping)
- Well, I'm all
packed and ready.
- Nice suitcase.
Monogrammed and everything.
- Actually, I got it at
Mojo Nixon's garage sale.
- Ah.
You got nothing but
bags of rice in here!
- Yup, sure is good for ya.
It's bleached and enriched.
- I'll bleach and enrich you.
Say, Mike, could you
grab my bag here?
- Sure.
- Just put my stuff in
a bunch of these babies.
- Ah, I see.
You've got your dirty laundry,
and a Schmidt Beer sign.
- Of course.
- And a whoopee cushion.
- Yep, and the food I
cleaned out of the fridge.
- Oh, an opened tin
of smoked oysters.
- And there's some loose
paella on the bottom there,
if you want to dig in.
- You're not my new best friend.
Stop pestering me!
Scram, would ya?
Oh, for cryin' out loud...
- So, Tom, what are you gonna do
with all the spare yous you've
collected over the years?
- Oh, you know, I
just did a head count,
an boy, I've made
quite a few of me.
517 at the last count.
- Wow, yeah, that's
far too much you.
You should be limited
to one or less.
- Exactly.
So I'm just gonna enact
a self-destruct mechanism
I planted in all the mes, ha-ha!
Here goes!
(electronic beep)
(loud explosions)
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh boy.
Oh, what the?
(loud explosion)
- Wow.
- Dah!
Servo?
- He done blowed hisself up!
Well, more Earth
for us, I guess.
- What the?
- Oh, there's my remote!
Figures.
One of those dumb
mes got a hold of it
and started playing me.
- Well, are you sure you're you?
- Of course I am!
You could tell right
away if I wasn't.
Well, I better clear out the
rest of the mes before I go.
(electronic beep)
(loud explosion)
- Dah!
Servo?
- Right here, Mike.
Say, have you seen my
remote detonating device?
- Oh, man.
This may take a
while to sort out.
We'll be right back.
- Ah, there it is!
Well, here goes!
- Dahh!
(electronic beep)
(loud explosions)
- Your government, ever
vigilant, determined--
- [Mike] Terry, yech!
- To stamp out, to crush
the current crime wave,
has restored the death penalty.
- [Mike] And so
Sister Helen Prejean
pulls out a rifle and shoots.
- As a temporary
measure, of course.
(goofy sounds)
- Faced with this extreme
form of punishment,
the socially sick
elements of our society...
- [Servo] Look who's talking.
- By that, I mean criminals.
- Do you mean Diabolik?
- Diabolik?
I assure you this
individual whose very name
reveals his antagonism
to the established values
of our society will soon
be brought to justice!
- [Man] Finally!
We agree!
- [Crow] Who the?
- The criminal paranoid seems
to have dedicated himself
to a one-man fight
against our society.
(goofy laughter)
This black mark,
this manifestation
of exaggerated delinquency...
- [Mike] Dorothy!
- Has exceeded the boundaries
of rational behavior.
(mocking mumbling)
- Within or without
the beaten structure
that is the very basis of
our freedom and way of life.
- [Crow] (coughing) Awesome
press conference, man.
- He also seems to derive a
great of pleasure from me.
- [Servo] Here's the gap.
- Making fun of our
entire police force.
You certainly are not
gonna make a fool of me.
(man laughing)
- [Mike] Nice teeth!
- [Crow] What are you, British?
- [Servo] Take it off!
(woman laughing)
- [Crow] I really should
get a line of dialogue soon.
(reporters laughing)
- [Servo] Dan Quayle
announces his candidacy.
(obnoxious laughter)
- [Mike] He temporarily
turned lizard!
- [Servo] C'mon, more, we
haven't seen his epiglottis yet.
- [Crow] Well, it's their
mess, so they should.
(sirens wailing)
- [Mike] Gerrymandering,
actual footage.
- [Man] Inspector,
we've discovered
the center of the drug traffic.
It's one of Valmont's
night clubs.
We have it surrounded.
- [Servo] Sorry, I'm
having hallucinations here.
(psychedelic music)
Woooooo!
- [Mike] Whoa.
Uh, Gary, you're
trying too hard.
- [Man] The police, the police!
(sirens wailing)
- Cops!
It's all over, boys!
The club is surrounded.
You're all under arrest!
- [Crow] Even you
giant juice glasses!
(mysterious music)
- [Servo] Oh no,
abandoned ships!
Sebastian Junger
wrote a book about us!
- [Crow] Hey look,
it's my nest up there.
- [Mike] Oh yeah, I see it.
- [Servo] Cute.
- [Man] You promised
us the drugs!
- [Man] Yeah, where is it?
- [Man] I run the best...
- [Mike] Yeah, whoa!
Fishing has been good today.
- [Crow] It's too
rough to feed you!
Oh wait, you're
models, never mind.
You don't eat.
- They've been inside for hours.
Such a waste of us.
- [Man] Your opinion is--
- [Servo] Burt Bacharach's
put on some weight.
- [Mike] Ah, just surveying
my girl kingdom here.
- If you're not gonna
back us, Valmont,
we'll have to withdraw
form the syndicate.
- I'm sorry to hear
you say that, Frank.
- [Crow] You have a
terribly annoying voice.
- I said sorry.
What flowers would
you like me to order?
- [Servo] How about
Wayland Flowers, boss?
- No, no, really.
What flowers?
Frank?
- [Mike] Yeah, lilacs?
- You boys.
You don't know when to
put your heads down.
- [Servo] After
the test is done?
- We just wait for now.
We're outside of the
three-mile limit, luckily.
(siren blaring)
- [Mike] The SS Jo Anne Worley!
- [Valmont] Is that Stud coming?
- [Crow] I beg your pardon?
(sinister music)
- [Servo] Can I
have another Ho Ho?
- When?
- Last night.
- You say all the narcotics?
- [Mike] Are in
Keith Richards, yes.
- [Crow] Do you want to,
like, look at us or something?
- [Servo] Every one of
these guys is in sanitation.
(hard smack)
- [Mike] Fresh!
I saw you undressing
me with your eyes.
- It seems that you
brought bad news.
- [Crow] Girls, I'm about
to sweat through my suit,
if you want to watch.
(nail file shaving)
- Shut up!
- [Servo] Wow, he can
afford white owls.
- That's enough, Ginko.
- [Mike] Oh man, gotta go.
Oh, don't be occupied,
don't be occupied...
- Get lost.
- [Crow] Could you tell me
what floor housewares is on?
(electronic squealing)
- [Servo] Mmm, mmm, boy,
pencils are good, mmm.
(alarm buzzing)
- Ginko here.
- [Mike] Huge Tanhead here.
- This is Valmont.
- [Ginko] Valmont?
I have nothing to say to you.
- I'm calling you, inspector,
on behalf of law and order.
- Good.
- I love Jerry Orbach!
- I would like us to make a
little bargain, inspector.
- You know how I
bargain with your kind.
First, I put you in cages.
Then I teach you to
sing beautifully.
For once, we've
got special powers.
- [Servo] Zing.
- By getting you Diabolik alive,
and then you can arrest him.
- [Ginko] Well, well, at
last you got the idea.
(Mystery Science
Theater 3000 theme)
- Joe, give me the tape
recording of the meeting.
- [Servo] Our Promise
Keepers meeting.
- We've taken a democratic vote.
Five in favor of my plan.
And three against it.
(loud gunshots)
- I will throw my vote!
Don't shoot, please!
- [Crow] I'm gonna put a
piece of my tongue in there.
- DOn't shoot, don't shoot!
- Since you said
please, I won't shoot.
- Ahh!
- [Mike] Extreme
organized crime!
- [Valmont] Clean up.
- [Servo] If Northwest flight
attendants had their way...
- Oh, Ralph!
How nice.
- [Mike] Toni, get dressed.
- Fresh air--
- Scram.
- Sure.
- Now it's unanimous.
- [Servo] Cavernous
noses are the best.
- So...
- [Mike] Should
we watch Sounder?
- These new emergency powers.
Ginko is really
putting the heat on us.
If we don't play ball with him,
we all wind up behind bars.
- [Crow] Or waiting tables.
- So we play ball, but how?
- We catch Diabolik for him.
We got the know-how
that the cops don't.
- No one's ever seen
Diabolik or his girl.
No one's ever seen
them and lived.
- So what?
(hoarse wheezing)
We got connections.
We all know squealers.
If all of us work
together on this...
- [Mike] We can wipe out litter.
- So long, Diabolik.
- [Crow] Just airing
out the little sizzler.
(sensual music)
- [Servo] Phyllis
Diller dropped by.
(stifling sneeze)
- [Mike] Plumber pulled
this out of the tub drain.
♪ Dee dee dah
- [Crow] Diabol-lick.
- [Servo] Honey,
I'm out of cash.
Wanna roll around in
some savings bonds?
- You've been
asleep for 20 hours.
- 20 hours?
- I slipped you a sleeping pill.
- Why?
- [Crow] When you're asleep,
you don't talk to
me or touch me.
- When you're not planning,
I'm afraid you get restless.
I'd rather have you sleep.
- [Servo] Hey, her
hair has a navel!
- [Mike] Ah,
they're co-gargling.
(machine buzzing)
- Excuse me, dear, I'm
expecting something.
- What?
- Watch.
- [Crow] Hef taught
me that move.
- The Foreign Office
today confirmed
the upcoming official visit of
British Finance Minister,
Sir Harold Clark.
Sir Harold and his
charming wife, Lady Clark,
will arrive here on
Thursday, May 5th.
- May 5th.
Isn't the 6th your birthday?
- [Servo] We're going over
to the Andersons for dinner.
- What would you
like me to give you?
- [Mike] Hmmm,
something non-penis.
- There must be
something I haven't got.
- [Reporter] A reception
is planned in their honor
in historic St. Just Castle.
Lady Clark will wear the
famous Aksand necklace
which is comprised
of 11 emeralds,
the most perfect in the world.
- Those emeralds.
- [Servo] Typical guy,
doesn't pick up the hint.
(mysterious jingle)
- [Man] You've arrived.
- [Mike] Wow, the
addition blends right in.
- [Crow] Got tickets?
Need two.
- You got the time, baby?
- Depends, handsome.
So far I've turned
down all offers.
- Why?
What's your price?
- [Servo] Are you planning
to buy me in bulk?
- An emerald necklace.
- [Mike] You're not gonna
give me the time, are you?
- You look worth it.
Hop in.
- [Crow] "You look weathered."
What a nice thing to say.
- [Servo] Look out!
- Well?
- [Mike] A young Sam
Donaldson scores.
- Lady Clark's room is...
Is the highest window,
the one that's lit up.
- And?
- [Crow] That building
looks like us.
- I saw a truck delivering
some television equipment.
- Closed-circuit TV.
- [Servo] Ali/Spinks tonight.
- Many police?
- About 50 outside.
And 30 inside
dressed as waiters.
- Hmm, and Ginko's the chef.
- I didn't see Ginko.
- [Mike] That squares my chin.
- If you didn't see
him, he's there.
- Huh?
- Anyone notice you?
- Oh, one of the
girls on the sidewalk
asked me a few questions.
She thought I was trying
to move in on her beat.
- I figured Diabolik would
make a play for those emeralds.
- Who wouldn't?
They're beautiful!
- Dry up, stupid!
- (laughing) Sure.
- [Crow] She's a sex clown.
- This might be our big chance.
If you're right, I'll
take care of you, sweetie.
- Want me to describe her?
- [Servo] Who's
straight in this scene?
- Not to me, to Tony.
Tell him!
- [Mike] Time for blood
pressure check, gentlemen.
- [Woman] Well, look at that.
That's a funny-looking thing.
(goofy laughter)
What is it?
Hey, I'm talking to you!
- You'll see, and
don't touch it.
- [Mike] Guys, he sees us!
- Whoa, hey!
- Did she have a face...
- Huh?
- Like this?
Was her face like this?
- No, like this.
- Okay, let's go on, her eyes?
(mysterious music)
- [Crow] No, no, stop
there, stop there.
No, no, wait, go back.
Go back.
No, it was not like
that, what'd'ya doin'?
No, no, that one, that one.
D'oh!
- [Servo] No, she wasn't Hitler!
- [Mike] This is actually
Electric Ladyland.
- Yeah, yeah, that's her!
Just like real.
- Get 5,000 copies of this
printed and circulate them.
She will not get away!
- [Crow] Cleopatra
drives a Jaguar.
- Good night.
- Good night, so
nice to see you.
- [Servo] Thanks
for helping us move.
- Good night.
Good night.
- [Mike] I finished
the magic flute.
- Boy, glad that's over.
- I hope it's not.
Why do you think I gave the
necklace all that publicity?
He'll never be able to
resist those emeralds.
Now we'll sit back and
wait to spring the trap.
- [Crow] Oh, can't
the Navy SEALs
ever just come in
the front door?
- [Servo] Wife
drops her earring...
- [Mike] Clunk.
- [Crow] Let's go
security guarding now,
where everybody's learning how.
Come on and security
guard with me!
- [Servo] I'm a Nazi,
but I love color!
What can I do?
(waves splashing)
- [Mike] I hurl my
skinniness at you!
- [Crow] Stupid jerk!
- [Servo] Wait, I'm
just the postman!
- [Mike] I exfoliate
while I creep.
- [Crow] Omaha Beach, June 5th.
I was early.
- [Mike] Look at that,
he's got knives stuck
in every cranny.
- [Servo] I'm just a neighbor!
- [Mike] You gotta
get rid of that cyst.
- Sir Harold...
- Are you dead?
- If you don't mind, I'd like
to check your room again.
- Please do.
- How romantic.
It makes me feel I'm living
in the days of highway robbers.
- [Mike] Hang on (snoring).
- When I return to London,
I will have such exciting
things to tell to my friends.
- [Crow] C'mon, honey,
I want you, baby!
Get moving!
- [Servo] My butt is weird.
- [Mike] Now for my
ACME Giant Pogo Stick.
- [Crow] I hate when
the party is done
and you just got a couple
old people left over.
(Servo vomiting)
- [Crow] Look out!
- No danger on this side.
Slippery wall straight down.
A fly couldn't climb it.
Lady Clark, may I ask you
to leave your necklace
on this table all night?
Part of our security
arrangements.
- Why, of course, inspector,
anything you'd like.
- Now I wish you
both good night.
- Bye-bye, to you.
- Good night.
- [Mike] Come along, Vivaldi.
- [Servo] You're gonna play
the Montgolfier brothers.
- [Mike] Hey, he's
double-bagging himself.
- [Crow] Now I'm gonna put a
nice red one over this one.
(tense music)
- [Servo] Brought his Lars
Tetens cigars with him.
That's good.
- [Mike] Oh boy, this is
gonna take a long time.
- [Crow] Yup.
Ah, he's just skittering
up the wall, isn't he?
- [Servo] He needs
Wallace's trousers.
- [Mike] I'm getting
a funny feeling.
- [Crow] Scraping
sounds reverberate
throughout the castle.
(helicopter whirring)
- [Servo] Help?
- How amusing they are.
- They're the police!
- I know, dear.
- [Servo] Are you nude yet?
- [Lady Clark] Oh, I feel
so marvelously attractive!
I did do good, didn't I, dear?
- [Harold] Yes, dear.
- It was a nice
evening after all.
- [Crow] That's right, be old.
- He never took his eyes
off my decollete once
the entire evening.
- [Servo] Howells
got a spin-off.
- [Lady Clark] Don't be nasty.
(Mystery Science
Theater 3000 theme)
- Huh?
Oh.
- Hey, Mike!
Does Pearl offer any kind
of a severance package?
'Cause as soon as we
get down to Earth,
I'm gonna need to buy a
blue suit for interviews,
and I'll probably want to blow
15 large on off-track betting!
- Oh, hang on.
Hey, Pearl?
(shredder whirring)
- Can it wait?
I have to explode
the nuclear core,
release all the mutants,
and fill out the change
of address cards.
Oh, oh, hey, Brain Guy.
Start pitching viruses
while I shred documents.
- I've got a million things to--
Oh, very well.
- Yes, sir, Nelson.
I don't even care that
you're coming back to Earth.
I took me a sweet job as
dictator for life of Qatar.
Now, they've been
courting me for some time.
They've even sent me
this beautiful basket
of flavored sand.
Look at that, Qatar!
My first act is to
get these idiots a U!
And, Brain Guy?
Brain Guy could care less, too.
He's got lots of stuff
going on, right, snow crab?
- Oh, yeah.
Hell yeah, in fact.
I've got lots of stuff going on.
- Yes, see, lots of stuff.
Big white guy like
him, you kidding me?
- Actually, though,
I was wondering
if you guys would be interested
in getting a place
together after this?
- Ooh, sorry, I actually have to
live in Qatar to rule over it.
Oh, plus, you smell,
and I don't like you?
- Naturally.
Bobo, what about you?
- Oh, you see, that's not
gonna work out for me.
I just took myself an
important position at the zoo.
Yup, had me a killer interview,
although I thought I'd blown it
when I charged the nice lady
and relieved myself on her desk.
But it turns out they want
me to start right away.
In fact, they pursued me.
Nets and stun guns, and
I had to lightly maul
one of my new coworkers.
Anyway, it's free
room and board.
Besides, I'm too
important for you now!
Ha, hahaha!
- I guess I'll have
to take that position
as the all-knowing eternal
and universal consciousness
over in Rylos-14, then.
- What a loser!
Oh, anyway, Mike, you were
asking me about severance.
That's on page 74
of your handbook.
- Oh, okay, I see, got it.
(alarm buzzing)
We got Movie Sign!
(doors opening)
(sonar beeping)
- [Servo] Choke.
Whoa, leave me alone,
you horny old goat!
- [Mike] Hello?
(dramatic music)
- [Crow] There are no coasters!
- [Servo] Happy Halloween,
I came as Powder.
(mysterious music)
- [Mike] After this score,
I'll be able to
reupholster myself.
- [Crow] Hmm, subtle!
- [Servo] It takes
a buto dancer.
- [Mike] The inside of his suit
is just filthy with bronzer.
- [Servo] Man, I hope
my nougat coating
doesn't wash off
on the trip back.
- [Mike] I'll take the picture
using the largest
camera in the world.
- [Lady Clark]
Harold, do you think
perhaps you should take a tonic?
- [Crow] 11, Mississippi.
12, Mississippi.
- [Mike] That's this room!
I'd know it anywhere.
- What?
- [Servo] Wa-wa.
- What is it?
- Went blank!
- [Harold] Do you
think the frowst
would have had the rhubarb?
- [Lady Clark] Oh,
rhubarb, rhubarb, rhubarb!
That's all you think about!
Harold, don't be ridiculous
and do come to bed.
- [Harold] I think I
need a new pair of pumps.
I think my feet must be growing.
(shrill scream)
- [Crow] Salieri, Mozart,
Scarlatti, you're with me!
Come on.
- My necklace, my beautiful,
beautiful emeralds.
- [Servo] Diabolik's only
two feet down the tower,
going as fast as he can.
- [Crow] The camera adds
10 pounds to a room.
(loud gunshots)
- [Servo] The old couple's
finally having it out.
(loud gunshot)
- Diabolik!
- [Mike] Left my
suction cups in the can.
What was I thinking?
(loud gunshot)
- [Crow] He has got to
be a bag of sweat by now.
(door slams)
- [Servo] Oh, this is what
they apult their cats with.
(rapid gunfire)
- [Crow] Kapellmeister,
break the door!
(loud gunshot)
(dramatic music)
- [Mike] I guess they like
to launch their
fruit occasionally.
- [Crow] Step aside, Voltaire.
(loud gunshot)
- [Servo] A flying mummy!
(loud gunshots)
I got him!
I know I did!
- Let's go and see.
- [Mike] If you got
him, you get a pistol.
(ethereal music)
- [Crow] Okay, I'm nude and I'm
still trapped in the castle.
Hmm.
(waves splashing)
- [Mike] Could you hold my hand
while we watch the sunset, sir?
- We've been had again.
We must get word to all patrols.
If he's escaping by car, they'll
stop him at the roadblocks.
- They'll never expect
us to double back.
We've done it again.
You are hurt.
Have Doc Vernier look
at that tomorrow.
- [Servo] But I'm
bleeding pretty bad now.
- [Mike] No, wait 'til tomorrow.
- What'll it be, ma'am?
- Fill it up, please.
- Sure thing.
- [Crow] Okay, Mr. Diabolik!
- [Servo] She's dressed
like Sheridan Liqueur.
- [Mike] So, Europe just looks
like Hampshire, Illinois.
- [Crow] Take that little
thing on the roads, pal,
you'll be in the grill of an SUV
before you can say buongiorno!
- [Servo] Stupid cop.
- [Mike] I'm beginning
to doubt my comb-over.
- [Crow] Hmm, I think
I'll get a teriyaki jerky.
- [Servo] Well, I'm done
showing men what worms they are.
- The tiger's in
the tank, ma'am.
- Keep the change.
- Thanks.
Would you like a
tail for good luck?
- Oh no, thank you,
I'm not superstitious.
(engine revving)
- [Mike] I should rub myself
with new car scent
and ask her out.
- [Servo] She's getting away!
What'll I do?
- [Crow] He's wearing
his tropical tweets.
(birds tweeting)
- [Servo] Oh man
(chewing noises),
swimming is great exercise.
- Hey, you!
Dang, knock it off, will ya?
- [Mike] Ah, we are
having fun, aren't we?
- [Crow] (chewing
noises) Gimme more.
- [Servo] The pool's
all cluttered with
Sociables and dip.
- Ralph!
Phone.
- [Mike] I'm coming, Alice.
- Ralph!
- [Crow] I need you to
razor my corns again!
- It's about time.
- [Servo] You shouldn't
get out of the pool
until an hour after he's eaten.
- It's a man.
- Shut up.
- [Mike] You're welcome.
- Who is it?
- It's Rudy.
The girl you're after
is at Vernier's.
- Don't let her
out of your sight.
- Are you sure no one
followed you here?
- [Servo] Who's who?
- Why do you ask?
- Listen to me, don't
come here again, ever.
- [Crow] Or I'll thrust
my forehead at you.
- What are you
trying to tell me?
- You came here
for medical advice.
I'm telling you this for
your health, and mine.
- [Servo] Eat more vegetables.
- Nurse?
- [Nurse] Yes, doctor?
- Take her along to
the infrared room.
- [Mike] Oh, and
do all the work,
and make all the hard decisions
at one-fourth my salary.
- [Crow] Infrared room.
Mike, I beg you to get
us an infrared room, now!
- [Servo] Please,
please, please?
- [Crow] Please!
Infrared room?
- [Servo] Ma'am, you
want me to pop this?
- Now just relax.
I'm going to give you
the infrared treatment.
- [Mike] It's actually kind
of a infra-burnt orange.
- Excuse me.
The fuse must have blown.
- [Crow] I don't
blame it, mmm-hmm.
- [Servo] Would you like
a sample of Giorgio?
(sinister music)
- [Mike] The bunchy diety
look, sweeping Europe!
- [Crow] The death
of Gregg Allman.
- Well, he should
have called by now!
- Relax.
- [Crow] Don't do it.
- We've got him in a box.
He's too far gone on the girl.
- Is she very beautiful?
- Yeah.
- Ooh!
- You're too smart to
ask stupid questions.
- [Servo] No, I'm not!
- Hold it.
- [Mike] Glad I
paneled the basement.
Now I can finally entertain.
(telephone ringing)
- [Crow] He's stringing
up some speakers.
It's gonna be great.
- [Servo] Bad guy.
- Enterprise one,
three-three-three.
- I saw your ad
regarding white Jaguar.
- [Mike] How new are the tires?
- What's your price?
- $10 million.
Plus...
- [Crow] Dealer and prep.
- An emerald necklace.
- Right.
- And don't try to pull any
of the funny stuff, huh?
I've got a couple of experts
at dealing with women here.
- [Servo] Dudley
Moore and Rick James.
- You might not find it too easy
to recognize her afterwards.
- [Mike] No, I was calling
about a white Jaguar?
- I accept your conditions.
- That's what I like to hear.
- [Crow] He has a
pillow top face.
- Yes.
Meet me at Sibby's at
the Break-In Airport.
- [Servo] He sounded nice.
- Get me Inspector Ginko.
- [Mike] Welcome, Dr. Meacham.
(foreboding music)
- [Crow] So you like my
cool conversion plane?
- [Servo] Ah,
they're gonna put him
over the trap door and
drop him three feet.
- [Mike] You had more than
one carry-on, you bastard.
- [Servo] I have a
flashing appointment.
Is this gonna take long?
(engine turning)
- Go check them.
- [Mike] It's full of Jean
Nate Friction Pour Le Bain!
- [Crow] We're seeing the
plane's private parts!
- It all seems to be here.
- [Servo] And I'm
a cartoon walrus!
- The necklace.
- When I've got Eva back.
- No necklace, no Eva.
That's the deal.
- Is that the only deal you've
got going today, Valmont?
- I don't have to talk.
- [Mike] I'd rather just cuddle.
I could kill you instead.
- Go ahead.
All you've got to do
is push that button.
- [Crow] That didn't have
the impact I'd hoped for.
- Valmont, this is
most unprofessional.
- [Henchman] Boss, we're
over the target now.
- [Servo] We need
any discount items?
- Circle this spot.
- [Henchman] Gotcha.
(intercom buzzing)
- [Crow] Excuse me.
- That's where Eva is.
- [Mike] Boss, you look
chilly, so I brought you this.
- [Valmont] Ever jumped before?
- [Servo] Once, from
the teeter-totter, yeah.
- [Valmont] Nope.
First, the necklace.
Hold it.
I'll take it.
- [Mike] Well, I
was just reaching
for my snotty Kleenex, but sure.
- [Valmont] Now.
- [Crow] Eww, it's all
warm from your pocket!
(dramatic music)
- [Mike] Like I quickly showed
all three of your faces?
- [Servo] But I'm
an evil mastermind!
(everyone laughing)
- [Mike] Ha ha ha, this is fun!
- [Crow] My leg is
turning one-dimensional!
(loud explosion)
- [Servo] Peanut dust!
- I almost forgot.
When I stumbled,
I attached a magnetic
capsule to your plane.
- Who cares?
Pull the cord!
- [Mike] No, it's
"pull the string!"
- I know it's a trap, Valmont!
Is Eva down there or only Ginko?
- Yeah, yeah!
She's there, in the cabin!
- And Ginko, is Ginko
down there, too?
- Yeah, yeah!
- [Crow] Like whoa, man, yeah!
- [Servo] Great, it's
a picnic umbrella.
D'oh!
- [Mike] Wow, I really
missed Yankee Stadium.
(hard thud)
(guttural groan)
- [Crow] Ow, I crushed
all my Pringles.
- It's a trap.
Valmont's made a
deal with Ginko.
Are you all right?
- [Servo] If my wig
is straight, I'm fine.
- Damn you, Ginko.
- [Mike] There's people
coming, I gotta straighten up.
- [Crow] Rat Patrol, too?
Man!
- [Servo] Oh, they're
trucking in Nittany Lions.
- [Crow] Is it too
windy back there?
- [Mike] Next birthday, I'm
taking you to Olive Garden.
(heavy breathing)
- You hide back in the cabin.
I'll draw their fire.
If they get me, you
know what to do.
- [Crow] Hook up with
some other idiot?
- But--
- Run, or they get us both.
- [Servo] Okay,
I'll go find Nova
and hang with her for a while.
(tires screeching)
- [Mike] Thought you guys were
gonna take the coast road.
Where'd you go?
- Inspector, we've
got him this time.
He's surrounded.
- [Crow] Ha, they don't know
about my pencil-thin arms!
(rhythmic primal music)
- [Servo] George, George,
George of the Jungle!
Strong as he can be.
- [Mike] Good job, tree.
Take it easy.
(rapid gunfire)
- [Crow] Ah-ha, I'll
give away my position!
Heh heh heh.
(rapid gunfire)
- [Servo] I was
cleaning the erasers!
(loud gunfire)
- [Mike] Hey, and I let
your ride on my parachute!
(loud gunfire)
- [Crow] I must remember to
have my face resharpened.
(ethereal music)
- [Servo] Damn,
I'm out of staples.
- I've got you, Diabolik.
Come on out.
- Valmont!
Don't play the hero!
- [Mike] Oh, Valmont
playing the hero.
Why does that not surprise me?
- [Servo] Your pacing is...
so...
important to a...
movie.
- [Crow] Eh, I'll
just try this again.
- [Servo] D'oh!
D'oh, d'oh, god,
gotta play the hero.
D'oh, oh, d'oh!
D'oh, ow!
(rapid gunfire)
- Now.
Diabolik!
Give up!
- [Mike] Yeah,
yeah, yeah, hang on.
I gotta get a Sen-Sen.
- [Crow] Damn
child-proof spy stuff!
- [Servo] My steel
reusable Fleet.
- [Mike] Maybe I can run real
fast and push it into him.
- [Crow] I wasn't
getting enough iron.
(mechanical click)
- [Servo] He swallowed
the silver thing.
We're sunk.
- [Mike] This could
be a long stand off.
I'd better take
care of, you know.
- [Crow] Uh, Spock,
are you going back?
- [Servo] Wonder if I can
see my backyard from up here?
- [Mike] Ah-ha!
Oh.
- [Servo] It's been
a hard day's night.
- [Crow] Diabol?
Diab, how you doing?
- [Servo] He's dead, I
have a huge forehead.
What else can go wrong?
- [Mike] Good night,
sweet thin guy.
- [Crow] A flight of Jaguars
sing thee to thy rest.
- [Servo] Oh, I suppose
he's young and has hair.
That means I'm just crap.
- [Doctor] So, this is
the famous Diabolik?
- [Assistant] Yes, doctor.
- Get him ready.
- Yes, sir.
(busy chatter)
- Is it true he's dead.
- Yes.
- Was he poisoned?
- Dr. Ferrara is
performing the autopsy.
- [Servo] I'm playing gearshift.
Vroom, vroom, heh heh.
- We'll begin with
a circular incision.
Scalpel.
(instruments jingling)
- [Crow] Oh, that's a scalpel?
Oh, I'll use that.
- [Mike] Ugh, let me get
that nose out of the way.
Just give me a
little room to work.
(dramatic music)
- [Crow] Here, I'll do
my own autopsy, thanks.
- [Servo] I'm not
Werner Klemperer!
Please don't hurt me!
- [Mike] You know, Quincy
wouldn't take crap like this.
- [Servo] Right.
- Krushan, doctor.
The Tibetan lamas have
used it for 3,000 years.
It brings on a
state of suspended
animation for 12 hours.
But if you're not
given the antidote,
the apparent death becomes real.
- [Servo] Anyway, I'll
get back on the table.
- How long's it been, Eva?
- [Crow] Well, it
shrank when you died--
Oh.
- 11 hours and 57 minutes.
- [Mike] Give or take 11 hours.
(Mystery Science
Theater 3000 theme)
- Sergeant.
- Lick me.
- This is our friend
Valmont's certificate.
- [Mike] He completed
Piano Book One.
- Cause of death, 11
machine gun shots.
11 emeralds.
- [Servo] And one pimple.
- 11 bullets.
To the morgue!
- [Crow] I'm really hungry.
- There, Ralph Valmont.
If you'll just sign this here,
here, here, and here.
- Four times.
- Four times, yes.
- [Mike] See,
Anonymous P. Hancock.
- [Crow] I'll take a
pack of Marlboros, too.
- He was basically a good boy.
Always sent money to mama.
- [Servo] Hang on, pig oyster.
- There there, buck up.
- [Crow] I'll see if I
have this in your size.
- [Mike] Mmm, the
baked beans are ready.
- He'll soon be home at last.
He's in peace now.
Let's see whether
he's ready yet.
Please.
- [Servo] I put some
semolina flour in him,
so he'll have a
nice, crispy crust.
- Yes, he's ready.
- [Crow] For some football!
- Every time...
- [Mike] I'm about to close,
some jerk wants to be cremated.
- I reflect on man's insig--
(sinister laughter)
Have you ever seen a--
(loud clang)
- Excuse me, could
you tell where the--
- [Servo] So no, then, I guess?
- [Crow] Let's face it,
this guy operates on
unbelievable luck
and coincidence.
- [Servo] Yep.
- Excuse me, please, could you
tell me where the doctor is?
- He's in shock.
- What?
- [Mike] But I have an
appointment to be cremated!
(cane tumbling)
- [Servo] Mein
Fuhrer, I can walk!
(sensual music)
- Good.
Don't look.
- [Servo] Ooh hoo!
- [Crow] You know,
sometimes O-rings can twist
and lose their
structural integrity.
Ah, who am I kidding?
It's not gonna happen.
- [Servo] No, that's all I got.
- [Diabolik] Two.
- [Mike] Two breast
emeralds, ha-ha-ha!
- [Diabolik] Three.
Four, five, six.
- [Crow] Right, right, seven,
eight, right, right, right.
- Eight.
Nine.
- Ten.
- Happy birthday.
- [Servo] Yeah, what
else could he get me?
- Oh, you shouldn't
have, darling.
- [Crow] Well, last year, he
just went to the gas station
and got some of those underpants
folded up like a rose.
- [Mike] World-record
pencil eraser.
- [Servo] I'll start
my Russian dance
as soon as you're done here.
- Inspector, we followed your
instructions to the letter.
20 tons of gold melted
into one big ingot.
Nobody in the world
could possibly steal it,
considering the weight.
- Uh-huh, yes.
- [Mike] Whip it good, everyone.
- You'd have to sweat for
two days to open that.
- [Crow] I remain
cool and dry, sir.
- Of course, our gold reserves
certainly have
dwindled recently.
- [Servo] And someone's
been taking paper clips.
- Only since everyone
stopped paying taxes.
We have to sell the gold
to get hard currency.
- [Crow] Ooh, I'm glad
he said "currency."
- [Mike] Oh, don't say goodbye.
- Arm the convoy!
- [Servo] Chicken in the
breadpan, pickin' up dough.
- [Ginko] Operation Gold Van.
Operation Gold Van.
This is Inspector
Ginko speaking.
Can you read me?
Over.
- I read you loud
and clear, over.
- [Ginko] The trains left.
I will be calling you
at 10-minute intervals.
Over and out.
(train horn blowing)
- [Mike] Sounds like my
uncle blowing his noise.
- Keep alert.
- [Crow] Nazis commute to work.
- Danek.
- Yes, sir?
- Take over up front.
- Yes, sir.
- [Servo] Yes, I'm king
of the front of the train!
Woo-hoo!
- [Crow] Whew, I wish we
Europeans believed in showering.
- [Mike] How long does it
take for breadsticks to bake?
- [Servo] Would've thought
one of these networks
would have put the other
out of business by now.
- [Mike] Hey, Hans, crack
that window, will ya?
- Five.
- [Crow] Crap, what's
the next number, again?
Five...
- Attention.
Attention.
Operation Gold Van.
- [Servo] Paging Mr. Herman.
- [Ginko] To all patrols
along the line, attention.
Train is underway.
Red flash alert.
Report all suspicious movements
in vicinity of right of way.
Arrest all persons
loitering along tracks as--
- [Servo] We gotta do it.
- [Mike] Don't loiter
near the tracks.
- [Crow] Nope.
- [Servo] Attention.
- [Ginko] DO you
read me, Patrol 39?
- Uh-huh, Patrol
39 acknowledging.
We're proceeding with plan.
(doors slamming)
(sonar beeping)
- Hey, and there's me by
the giant fiberglass muskie
in Hayward, Wisconsin.
- Wow, Mike, I can't wait to see
all the wonders of
your amazing planet.
- Yeah, me neither.
You know, Crow is gonna love--
Hey, Crow!
Cr--
- Crow?
- (sobbing) Mike,
I don't wanna go.
I'm scared!
- I think he wedged
himself under the desk!
- Oh, brother.
Come on outta there, you big
lily-livered scaredy Earth!
- Hey, come on, take it easy.
What's the matter, little pal?
- Well, well, the
Earth is so big,
and there's traffic accidents,
and all those open spaces,
and there's wild pigs.
I wanna stay here.
- Yeah, I thought
this might happen,
so I wrote a little song.
Kinda help with the jitters?
Servo, Gypsy, will
you help me out?
- Well, lay on, Cole Porter!
(gentle piano music)
♪ I know it's hard to leave
♪ This little satellite of ours
♪ We've had some fine adventures
♪ We danced among the stars
- We did!
♪ And though we're
far-out space nuts
♪ No matter where I roam
♪ There's just no other planet
♪ Like the planet I call home
- Wisconsin?
- No, actually, I was
talking about this...
♪ To Earth
♪ The very birthplace
of my birth
♪ The thought of Earth
fills me with mirth
♪ Hey, maybe we'll
meet Colin Firth
♪ That is a possibility
♪ See
♪ The blossoms on an apple tree
♪ To wander barefoot by the sea
♪ And slice your heel upon a
broken bottle of Lipton Ice Tea
- C'mon, clam it, shorty,
you're not helping.
♪ The Earth's a
big and scary place
♪ With wars and crime and gas
- It is?
♪ They listen to Shawn
Mullins and Alanis Morrissette
- Oh no!
♪ This satellite
has been my home
♪ I've never known another
- Me either!
♪ Where will I
live, what will I do
And can I keep my mother?
- Absolutely
- Mom!
♪ Okay
- Oh no!
♪ Then it's to Earth
we'll go to stay
♪ Through sylvan glens
we'll romp and play
- Yeah!
♪ Oh, but what if I
get eaten by a dog
♪ Or by a manta ray
♪ Let's go
♪ There's so much
that we don't know
♪ It's Gypsy, Servo,
Mike, and Crow
♪ I'm scared of water buffalo
♪ Exotic lands
we'll come to know
♪ We'll all get
mauled in Chicago
♪ We'll bid the
satellite farewell
♪ And then we'll go to Earth
♪ Well, now I think
I'd rather stay
♪ To Earth
♪ I wish to hell
you wouldn't say
♪ To Earth
- Well, now I can't wait to go!
Show me that giant
fiberglass muskie!
- That's the spirit!
Hey, Tom, where was that pic--
Tom, Tom?
- I think he wedged
himself under the desk.
- Uh-oh.
- Great.
Now I'm gonna have to
write a whole new song.
We'll be right back.
- Help?
(Mystery Science
Theater 3000 theme)
(upbeat music)
(Servo humming)
- [Crow] Sorry, ma'am, I'm gay.
- [Mike] Oh, I wore
that hitchhiking once.
- [Crow] Yeesh.
- Can I help you?
- Oh, thanks, I
could use a lift.
- [Trucker] Yeah, sure!
- [Servo] If I could
borrow that belt.
- I ran out of gas.
Oh, I'm so tired.
If you could just drop
me at the motel, huh?
- Yeah.
- I'll worry about the
car in the morning.
- [Crow] In my skimpy nightie.
- Oh, oh, my suitcase!
- I'll get it.
- [Servo] I borrowed
Harvey Fierstein's voice.
- Happy to get it.
- Oh, you're so nice.
(raspy croaking)
- It's heavy.
- Always glad to help
a lady in distress.
- [Mike] I bought the largest
toddler jumper I could find.
- [Servo] Would you
stop being stealthy
and just get in the truck?
- [Crow] Turns out Diabolik
can't drive a stick.
- [Mike] I usually
wear my driving thong.
(engine turns)
(upbeat music)
♪ It's not unusual to
steal trucks from anyone
(musical scatting)
- [Mike] This is so Mentos-y.
- Stop it!
Stop!
- [Crow] Oh, crap, I'm
supposed to be driving!
- [Servo] Wa-ha!
- [Mike] Ah, Diabolik
adds to his trail
of charred and
dismembered bodies.
(loud crash)
- [Crow] George
Jones drives a truck.
(downtrodden music)
(uptempo surf rock music)
- [Servo] We're beautiful
and you're a loser!
- [Crow] Ah, it's
delightful and charming
that they triumphed
again in the name of sex.
- [Mike] Hey, can I get a
ride with you, okay fine.
(loud gunshots)
- Requesting aid, repeat.
- Ginko here.
Ginko here!
- [Servo] Ginko here!
- What's happened?
(brakes grinding)
- [Crow] Reginald
Perrin's on that train.
- [Mike] Flaming truck at
Brixton, 20 minutes late, Joan.
- He's probably mined the
entrances to the tunnel.
We can't afford to take chances.
- [Servo] We've drained
the chances-taking budget.
- We're backing out before--
(loud explosion)
- [Mike] Oh wait, no, we're not.
(humming upbeat music)
Just as I thought.
The tunnel's been blocked
by two explosions.
Luckily, we're clear.
- [Crow] Are we
still on for dinner?
- Danek's in pursuit.
The train will have
to be rerouted.
- Wait.
Three miles back, there's the
Arleville marshaling yard.
From there, take the unused line
that crosses the bay
on the Lawrence Bridge.
- [Mike] I'll hit the
slot machine first.
(uptempo surf rock music)
♪ I only learned one lick
♪ Does it bug you at all
♪ Gotta practice my lick
♪ Only one hour more
- [Servo] Listen, someone's
beating up Doc Severinsen.
- [Crow] Hey-oh!
- [Mike] Ah, that
was a great finch.
- Perfect, Ginko, perfect.
- [Servo] Whoopee!
(tires screeching)
- [Crow] Ah, should have
gotten a sleeper car.
I didn't know this movie
would take so long!
- [Servo] Man, Von
Ryan really fell bad.
- [Mike] Bye-bye, Von Ryan.
- [Crow] Bye.
(loud explosion)
- [Mike] Oh, more
innocent people killed
because of Diabolik's whims.
- [Servo] How wonderful.
(loud splash)
- Something happened?
- [Servo] No.
- Headquarters to
Operation Gold Van.
Headquarters to
I can't hear you.
YOu're drowned out.
- [Crow] The ocean is
heavily chlorinated.
(water splashing)
(languid music)
- [Mike] I put this rope up so
the sharks stop bothering me.
- [Servo] Wait, she's a man!
Ugh, yuck.
- [Crow] Ah, he found
the ocean's plug.
Now he's gonna drain it.
- [Mike] And bring those
paper towels over here.
I spilled a little.
- [Servo] I don't
think the rain gear
is gonna help at this point.
- [Crow] My tanks are filled
with Paul Mitchell products.
(air hissing)
- [Mike] Sorry.
♪ La la la la
♪ Wa wa wa wa
- [Crow] Lyrics by Chachi.
- [Mike] You know, I heard
the song as wee-wee-wee.
This is kind of an
interesting interpretation.
♪ Waa waa waa
- [Servo] Woo!
Man, I'm farting
a mile a minute.
- [Crow] You're a zero!
- [Servo] Hey!
- [Crow] What?
- [Crow] What, Mike,
what do you want?
- [Mike] No, I...
Nothing, never mind.
- [Servo] Kinda hard to
drive with fins on, isn't it?
- [Crow] Uh, how do
you start this thing?
♪ Waa waa, waa waa
- [Mike] Hey, that's Fonzie
joining in with the whoa-whoa.
- [Crow] Release
baking soda, and away!
- [Servo] Raising the
Titanic would be a cinch!
Just get a bunch
of party balloons.
- [Crow] You know,
nobody goes through
this kind of trouble any more
for frankincense or myrrh.
- [Servo] Oh.
Ribbit, sir.
- Well?
- [Frogman] Nothing, inspector.
The gold's not there.
I searched everywhere.
- Why, what do you
mean it's not there?
It weighs 20 tons!
- [Mike] If it's heavy,
it has to be there!
- [Crow] What do you
mean it's not there?
It's blue!
- [Servo] Diabolik really
likes to tinker in his garage.
- [Crow] Honey, are
you gonna come up?
I made you a ham sandwich.
- [Mike] He's on the David
Cassidy workout program.
- [Crow] Boy, labelmakers
have really come a long way.
- Ahh, I'll put
it right in here.
- [Servo] I wish more gold
would get this test done.
It would save a lot of lives.
- Good.
This laser gun
can melt anything.
Except you, honey.
Nice that gold melts at a
lower temperature than steel.
It's the only way we can get it.
- [Mike] "Oh, I'm gold,
I'm hard to steal."
Well, eat me, gold!
- [Crow] Can I get
you a cappuccino, sir?
(phone buzzing)
- Ginko here.
- Inspector.
- [Servo] I'm Mr. Wilson.
- We allowed you take all
these extravagant measures
so that the gold would reach
its destination without fail!
And now, what do I hear?
What am I to report
to the minister?
What is he to tell
to Parliament?
That we are bunch of
helpless jackasses?!
- Let's not exaggerate.
- Exaggerate?
Don't be funny!
- [Mike] Like Fred
Travalena, sir?
- Well, professor.
- [Professor] Yes, yes?
There are spots.
- Good, there are traces.
- Traces of what?
- [Servo] Love?
- Radioactivity.
As a precaution, I had
part of the container
holding the gold radioactivated.
- [Mike] Let's not talk.
- Then there's a chance
of recovering it!
(Mystery Science
Theater 3000 theme)
- You be careful.
- Don't worry.
With this suit, I could swim
through the center of the sun.
- [Servo] Well, that's what it
said in the catalog, anyway.
- [Mike] Wow, that
enhugens his face.
- [Servo] Mmm, canker sore.
- [Crow] Oh, wow,
wow, turn it down!
You're getting gold everywhere.
- [Mike] The government's
French dressing storehouse.
- [Servo] Remember when I
said that about the gold?
Feels great, that's great.
(diabolic laughter)
- [Crow] Sorry,
drank too much coffee
and ate a lot of asparagus.
(foreboding music)
- [Servo] Ooh!
- [Mike] Oh, Dr.
Phibes is drunk again.
- The alarm.
- [Crow] The bed-wetting alarm.
What does it mean?
- Someone's broken in.
- [Servo] Let's go
swim through the sun.
- [Mike] Kinda glad I didn't
install a bagpipe alarm.
- [Crow] I need to get
out of this play suit.
- Run.
I'll meet you in
tunnel number seven.
They'll never find us there.
- Why aren't you coming now?
- I've got to open the locks.
- [Mike] And bagels.
- They'll drown like rats.
- I'll wait for you.
I'm not going alone!
- [Servo] Who will
inflate my lips?
- You are.
You'll not be
alone while I live.
- [Crow] You can
stay with my mom.
- Now go!
- [Mike] Keep going.
Keep--
Keep going further.
Go.
- [Crow] A box of men got out.
- [Servo] That suit has to
be a little constricting.
- [Crow] You know he's
taping and tucking.
- [Servo] He's gotta be.
(loud gunshots)
- [Mike] D'oh, my
own shotgun trap!
I keep forgetting.
(loud gunshots)
- [Crow] Okay, geez!
I gotcha.
(loud gunshots)
- [Servo] Kato, no!
(rapid gunshots)
(loud gunshots)
- [Crow] Well, I'm
sorry if you're offended
by my random murders.
(loud gunshots)
- [Mike] No, it's boiling over.
Now the house is gonna
smell like burnt gold.
- [Crow] Great.
Ha ha, I'm useless
against your weapons!
I mean...
(rapid gunshots)
- Diabolik!
You're finished!
The exits are blocked!
- [Servo] I'll bulge
my eyes at you!
(loud explosion)
- [Mike] Help, I forgot to wear
swimming-through-the-sun-proof
socks!
Ow!
- [Servo] Some kids get
covered with molten gold
when they sit and spin...
- [Crow] Suit didn't work
as well as I thought.
- [Mike] He's a golden Gumby.
♪ Gold everything
(general chatter)
- [Crow] What is that,
a pack of baboons?
(Servo grunting)
- Thank you very much.
- [Mike] Sir, is it true
you're dating Ben Affleck?
- Barbaric, displaying the
body of a fallen enemy.
- The minister.
Besides, it's good publicity.
(general chatter)
- [Servo] Isn't it cool?
You guys.
- [Crow] Kind of stupid to have
an underground observatory.
- Order this place
to be cleared.
- Yes, sir.
- [Servo] I'll fart.
- Everybody out, please.
- [Servo] I took
a Swizzle Stick.
- Alright, gentlemen, leave.
This way, please.
- [Mike] Ah, there
ain't no story here.
I'm just gonna write
about the Internet.
(general chatter)
- [Crow] These guys are
part of the Rhythm Nation.
Not entirely.
(dull droning)
(dramatic music)
- [Servo] They're
raiding my refrigerator!
- [Mike] And the movie
just kinds of peters out.
- [Crow] Well, let's
see if we can find
another hero somewhere else.
(melancholy music)
- [Mike] I'll sneak out while
he has no peripheral vision.
- [Crow] Did she get
stuck in a bear's behind?
- [Servo] Hmm, I thought I heard
someone laughing at my outfit.
Oh, well.
- [Crow] Well, this
place looks cavernous,
but it's only got a little
cramped kitchenette.
It's real pink.
Shouldn't the Sandpipers
start singing right about now?
- [Crow] Well, I'm
off to the Iditarod.
- [Servo] What's
that stain up there?
- [Mike] If only he'd been
drenched in zero coupon bonds.
- [Crow] Oh, I know you
stabilized our economy,
but it's hard to accept.
- [Servo] We had so many
innocent people left to murder.
Yeah.
(sinister music)
- Can You move your car?
You parked me in.
- I was expecting
you, inspector.
- [Servo] I wasn't
expecting your expecting
when I expectorated your
injector, inspector.
- I knew you wouldn't be
able to resist seeing him.
- Please...
- [Mike] Get bent.
- Give me a few seconds more.
Alone.
- [Crow] Oh, man,
my nose itches.
- [Mike] Well, you guys
have never tricked me,
so I guess it's okay.
- [Servo] Oh, once this
giant mink gives birth to me,
I'll help you, honey.
- [Mike] Invest me wisely.
- [Crow] Hey, watch the hand!
(dramatic music)
- [Servo] (muffled) Woman, get
this stupid thing off of me!
- [Mike] Not to take
anything away from Diabolik,
but this guy was not the
sharpest arch-nemesis.
- [Crow] That's not to say
anything bad about Diabolik--
- [Mike] Not to take
anything away from him.
- Thank you, inspector.
You don't know
how grateful I am.
- [Crow] He's basically an
eyebrow delivery system.
- [Servo] Man, there's a cold
Heineken sitting right there!
♪ Deep, deep down
- [Mike] It doesn't really
seem like he comes out ahead.
- [Crow] Not really.
♪ Deep, deep down
(diabolic laughter)
- [Crow] Hey, who
turned off the lights?
- [Servo] This has been the
official biopic of Larry Fine.
(doors slamming)
(sonar beeping)
(alarm beeping)
- Tom, what's our situation?
- Beginning reentry, Mike!
- Good.
(loud explosion)
- Ugh!
Total heat shield failure, Mike!
- Bad.
What's going on?
- Deck Three broken away!
(loud explosion)
Deck Four broken away!
- Oh my gosh, Cambot, give
me Rocket Number Nine!
- Whoa, Nelly!
(loud explosions)
Deck Five broken away!
Deck Six, broken away!
(loud explosion)
Deck Seven, melting
and broken away!
- Gypsy, what do we do?
- We burn up horribly.
It's too dreadful
to contemplate!
Oh my god in heaven, please
have mercy on our souls!
- I'll call Pearl.
- Uh-oh, toxic gas filling our
lungs and our nasal passages!
- [Mike] Pearl!
- Now sing, dammit, sing!
♪ It's a long way
to tip a rare breed
- Look, Nelson.
Move on.
I am.
(electronic static)
- Whoa, Deck Nine crashing
through Deck 10 and 11!
- This is it!
We're going down!
(loud explosion)
- Brace for impact!
- We're all gonna die!
- Mike, have you seen
my other sweater?
(panicked screaming)
(loud crash)
(loud explosion)
(light music)
- Heh heh heh, boy, oh boy,
this ConGypsCo stock is up!
I mean, way up!
- Well, Gypsy did want to let
us in on her public offering,
but we said no.
- Well, if you remember,
I made a fart noise.
She only took it as a no.
- Well, still, it
all worked out.
I mean, we were very fortunate
to walk away from that crash.
- I'll say.
- Oh, yeah.
- I guess if we were
all multibillionaires,
you guys wouldn't
have moved in with me.
- True.
- Yeah, that's right.
Sweet garden-level living.
One bedroom, one half-bath,
and on the bus line.
- Sweet!
- Hey, who's for rice?
- Would you sit down?
The movie's about to start!
- Come here, dummy!
- [Announcer] WTMJ TV
in Milwaukee presents
our Saturday afternoon
movie, The Crawling Eye.
(dramatic music)
- The Crawling Eye, the
Marty Feldman story.
- [Mike] Oh, Forrest Tucker.
He's the guy that makes sure
the trees' shirt tails are in.
- This movie looks kind
of familiar, doesn't it?
- [Servo] Hmm...
(MST3K Love Theme)
(siren whooping)
- [Valmont] Is that Stud coming?